Adverts are designed to persuade us, but which techniques have been shown to be effective in enticing us to buy things?
广告旨在说服我们购买商品，但哪些技巧已被证实是有效的哪？
One way is simply to portray something as normal.
一种方法就是将某事物描绘成常态。
Former advertising professional Dan Parker explains that 'normalisation', showing people happily eating unhealthily, can lead to higher sales of junk food as people start to see these habits as normal.
前广告从业者丹·帕克解释说，“常态化”——展现人们开心地吃不健康食品——会使垃圾食品销量攀升，因为人们会开始将这些习惯视为正常。
This is like product placement, where products are shown or mentioned in TV shows and films.
这类似于植入式广告，即在影视剧里展示或提及产品。
Beth Fossen, an assistant professor of marketing, tells us that product placement is most effective when it is not too obvious.
市场营销助理教授贝丝·福森告诉我们，植入式广告在不那么显眼时效果最佳。
We become defensive if we know that someone is trying to sell us something.
如果我们知道有人试图向我们推销东西，就会产生戒备心。
It seems that a subtle approach can be more convincing.
似乎隐晦的方式更具说服力。
Appealing to our emotions is another strategy that advertisers use.
诉诸情感是广告商使用的另一种策略。
Some of them use fear to persuade us.
部分广告商会利用恐惧来说服我们。
Jannet Pendleton, a senior lecturer in communication studies, explains that for fear to be an effective tool, we need to believe that both the fears raised, and the possibility that our actions can make a difference are credible.
传播学高级讲师詹妮特·彭德尔顿解释说，要让恐惧成为有效工具，我们必须相信所引起的恐惧以及自身行动能带来改变的可能性都是可信的。
Where fears are exaggerated or we feel helpless, we are likely to switch off.
如果恐惧被夸大，或是我们感到无助，就很可能会抵触。
Adverts often show perfect-looking people because marketers believe that we will aspire to be like them and buy the products they endorse.
广告常展示形象完美的人，因为营销人员认为我们会渴望成为那样的人，并购买他们代言的产品。
However, as Karen Middleton, a senior lecturer in marketing and advertising, points out, this may not be the best strategy.
然而，市场营销与广告学高级讲师卡伦·米德尔顿指出，这或许并非最佳策略。
The research that she mentions shows these adverts can make people feel bad and put them off products.
她提及的研究表明，这类广告会让人产生负面情绪，进而对产品产生反感。
These studies say that seeing a more human and relatable side of people can sway us into believing them.
这些研究称，看到人们更真实、更易共情的一面，会让我们更愿意相信他们。
David Robson, writing for BBC Worklife, explains that endorsements from characters who admit their mistakes can often be more believable.
为BBC职场专栏撰稿的戴维·罗布森解释道，承认自身错误的人物所做的代言往往更可信。
So, it seems that the secret to these persuasion techniques is that, to be most effective, they need to be used carefully.
由此看来，这些说服技巧的关键在于，要想效果最佳，就必须谨慎运用。
Perhaps the best technique advertisers can use to persuade people is to fully understand the people they are selling to.
或许广告商能用来说服人们的最佳技巧，就是充分了解目标受众。